Following our conversation, here are the open items:
	#1.	Think if you want to remove the Local NDL from the launch screen (considering you added the IIS server)
	#2.	Games marked orange – see you if can find a better color  maybe dark blue – still noticeable, but not too much
	#3.	Filters list, arena columns – missing tooltips
	#4.	Filters list, add a restriction for max allowed of filters (I’d say 7 is enough)
5.	Mockups screen – replace the bottom dynamic layouts part with a dropdown, to choose from default, layout 1, layout 2.
	#6.	Allow renaming the dynamic layouts
	#7.	Dynamic layouts conditions – remove “change” from all dropdowns
	##8.	Allow duplicating content to a new dynamic layout, so you don’t have to start from scratch (as discussed – from scratch, from default, from another layout)
9.	Replace between lobby arena and games arena on the left bar – PLEASE IGNORE this one. I will talk to Or and Ofir first
	##10.	Add search bar to the games list on the right bar, and the games list in the center
11.	Double click on error would take to the relevant screen
	##12.	Allow adding multiple items at once (e.g. adding multiple games to an arena)
	#13.	Disable editing the live dealer arena
	#14.	On game lists inside an arena – remove all sort-by functionality
15.	Add the option to export the data to an XL file
16.	Add a warning message when the user tries to close the app without saving (see the end of the BRD for text)

I’ll check with Ofir & Or:
1.	Dynamic layouts condition no. of rounds works by game type - I’ll verify with Ofir that it’s OK
2.	I’ll ask Ofir how many dynamic layouts he needs (if 2 are enough)
3.	Player status is currently just IsVIP true/false – I’ll verify with ofir that it’s fine.
4.	I’ll consult the order of the items in the list on the left
